cwgdelhi2010.org 2014-12-02

# Privacy Policy | XIX Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi has created this Privacy Policy and Collection Statement (together referred to as this "Privacy Policy") in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to the privacy of your personal information.

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi is bound by the Information Technolony Act, 2000. Our website complies with the Information technology Act, 2000. Cookies are not presently used on the Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi website.

**Personal information collection**  
Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * information about transactions carried out over this website ;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services ; and
  * any other information that you send to Organising Committee, Commonwealth Games 2010, Delhi.

**Using personal information**  
Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi does not collect or record personal information, except that which you provide freely or that which is public information. Any information freely submitted may be recorded on our client contact database which is used to keep you up to date with our activities. For example from time to time 2010 Delhi Commonwealth Games may run competitions which will require entrants to submit information such as name, address, phone number, date of birth.

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi uses "Privacy Opt Out" clauses where necessary, which gives you the option to prevent personal information from being used to send you future materials about the Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi?

You may gain access to your personal information at any time or request us to destroy it or return it to you. You can also contact us to update your details. Contact information is provided below.

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi has security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information under its control.

These security measures include restricted access, password protection on databases and clauses in employee agreements requiring confidentiality.

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party without your consent. However, please note that if at any time Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi is required by law to release information about you or your organisation in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights. Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi may do so. .

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi will update this privacy policy as required. If it is changed, the changes will be posted on the Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi website ([www.cwgdelhi2010.org](http://www.cwgdelhi2010.org/)) so that you are always aware of the sort of information collected, how the information may be used, and under what circumstances it may be disclosed by Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you may contact us using the Contact Us form or as follows:

**Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi**

Organising Committee Commonwealth Games 2010 Delhi,   
New Delhi City Centre – Tower II,   
Opposite Jantar Mantar,   
Jai Singh Road,   
New Delhi 110 001.   
T: +91-11-24500400
